littleapp.in 2019-11-15

# Little - Privacy

#### Privacy Policy

  * What Personal Information Does Little Collect?

Your phone number.

Your location information from time to time.

Any personal information that you choose to provide such as name, email, gender.

Information about your device such as hardware information, operating system version, carrier info if available. Any information(mandatory-phone number. Optional information if user wishes to disclose- name, email, gender) collected from the end user is stored on servers of Little only. No information collected by Little from the end user will be sold/rented/shared with a third party.

  * ##### Why is this information collected?

Data collected from the end user (mandatory- phone number, optional- name, email, gender) is stored on Little Virtual Private Cloud hosted on Amazon Web Services. This data will be retained by Little till the end user sends an Account Deletion Request. Your Services account will be associated with your phone number and this account will be used for all our Services that you use. Information you provide to one of our Services may be used with other Services from us that you or your friends use. For example, location information we receive in connection with your use of one of our apps may be used to customize the content you and your friends see in another of our apps. We may also draw upon this Personal Information in order to adapt the Services of our community to your needs, to research the effectiveness of our network and Services, and to develop new tools for the community.The contact information you provide may be used by Little to send you timely and relevant promotions. By accepting this privacy policy, you give Little the right to contact you by SMS or e-mail for such promotions. The stored information is gauged by our system, if the purchases comply with our existing service’s Terms and Conditions then the customer is provided with a coupon for the making the subsequent purchase. Information is used to present customized offers to the end user.

Little provides you, the user, with deals in vairous categories which are highly customized to your location, indicated tastes and probable use. Since the deals are tim-sensitive, we need to collect the above information on a periodic basis. Your contact information is collected in order to enable you to share the deals that you discover on our platform with your friends at real-time.

  * ##### How is My Information Shared?

Personal Information about our users is an integral part of our business. We neither rent nor sell your indentifiable personal Information to anyone.

##### Friends and Followers:

Alive is a social engagement platform by Little. The end user can opt in based on his/her own discretion.

Friends on Little: Your friends can see, for example, your location (as described in more detail below).

Followers and people/brands you follow on Little: Followers can see your publicly available information and you can see the publicly available information of users you follow, as described below (under "Publicly Available Information and Apps").

Individuals reading this information may use it or disclose it to other individuals or entities without our control and without your knowledge. We therefore urge you to think carefully about including any specific information you may deem private in comments, plans or tips or other content (location or otherwise) that you create in the Services.

Businesses, Locations, Events and Brands: One of the key purposes of the Services is to help users learn about businesses, locations, events and brands (for example, a restaurant or a movie theater or a hotel) that are relevant to them, and for these entities to provide information about themselves, their locations and events to users, as well as to reward users when they visit their location or event through offers and specials.

Publicly Available Information: When you use the Services, certain information is public, such as your public user profile information, tips, likes, saves, public photos, lists that you create and save, tastes and lists of friends and/or followers (as applicable to a particular Service), and may be searchable by search engines and be shared with or disclosed to third parties, including through our API to a wide range of users and services. We may also share or disclose aggregated and anonymous data, such as de-identified location data, to third parties, including users you may follow and users of our Service, for analytical or other purposes.

  * ##### Determining your location.

The Services deal with location, so in order to work, the Services need to know your location. Whenever you open and use/interact with our apps on your mobile device or go to one of our Sites, we use the location information from your mobile device or browser (e.g., latitude and longitude) to tailor the Services experience to your current location (i.e., we'll show you a list of nearby locations, friends and tips). This information is NOT shared in a form that is identified with you with others unless you are using a service that they offer. Also, the Services use your mobile device's ‘background location to provide the Services, including to send you notifications of tips/friends/plans/interesting things etc. near you. If you have ‘background location turned on, the Little app will, from time to time, tell us about your device's location even if you are not directly interacting with the application. The user can enable/disable location services from their mobile device and use the Static Location service offered by Little App to select any location from a set of predefined locations.

  * ##### Sharing Location with the Little app.

Your real-time location is not shared with anyone on the Little app in a form that identifies you.If you use a service from one of our merchants, write a tip, like or otherwise interact with a place, users may infer that you have been to that location. Some content, like tips, are time stamped and other users could use that information to infer when you were at a place even though tips can be posted when you aren't at the place you are leaving a tip about.

Your location data is ONLY shared with others when you proactively decide to "purchase" a deal from one of the merchants on our platform. "Others" in this scenario ONLY represents the owner of the service / product that you have purchased.

By default, location sharing is turned on and at a radius level is shared with your Little friends and is updated from time to time using your background location. You can turn off neighborhood sharing. Your location is also shared when you proactively decide to "purchase with a "check in" is the location information of that place. Additionally, when you send a message on Little, your mobile device's location is shared with all recipients of the message.

  * ##### Your Location History

We store your location history to provide you better quality deals. This information is treated as private under any and all circumstances and is NEVER shared. The user can enable/disable location services from their mobile device and use the Static Location service offered by Little App to select any location from a set of predefined locations

  * ##### Customer grievances

Any grievances/complaints should be addressed to [support_littleapp@nearbuy.com](mailto:support_littleapp@nearbuy.com)
